In  India,  in
every  1 .89
seconds,  somebody  breaks
a  traffic  rule
and  this  is
due  to  a
silly  FA  called
Pissed  Under  effect.
You  know  it
very  well.  If
Ramu  is  not
stopping,  Raju  is
not  stopping  either.
Why  the  hell
should  I  stop?
A  red  signal,
who  are  80
%  of  accidents
are  caused  by
breaking  simple  traffic
rules,  like  not
wearing  helmets,  not
wearing  seat  belts,
driving  on  the
wrong  side  of
the  roads  or
jogging  on  folds.
This  causes  loss
of  1 .5
lakh  lives  every
year  that  could
be  saved  just
by  following  simple
traffic  rules.  Will
you  become  a
change  that  will
inspire  others  or
just  be  a
bystander  guy,  follow
traffic  rules  for
you,  your  loved
ones  and  your
countrymen?  Remember  the
bystander  effect.